<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christopher Gandrud ℈</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Christopher Gandrud ℈</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2020, Christopher Gandrud</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Letterlike Symbol of the Day: Scruple ℈</title>
      <link>/post/letterlike-symbol-of-the-day-scruple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/letterlike-symbol-of-the-day-scruple/</guid>
      <description>℈ scruple  a small unit in the apothecaries&amp;rsquo; system equal to 20 grains (wiki)
 My journey to the character Alexander Masters&amp;rsquo; A Life Discarded (2016) explores 148 diaries that his friends found in a skip in Cambridge. I&amp;rsquo;ve really enjoyed all of Masters&amp;rsquo; books; a loving biographies of Cambridge oddballs that makes that town seem about as eccentric and moldy as it likely is.
One great joy of the book is its tour of ~50 years of notebooks and the information they came printed with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management and &#34;The Elements of Surprise&#34;</title>
      <link>/post/management-and-the-elements-of-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/management-and-the-elements-of-surprise/</guid>
      <description>🏗 Basic idea A research team, a department, a company is at some fundamental level just:
 a bunch of people talking to each other
 Hopefully, when people talk to each other, they convey the meaning they intended to the people they are talking to. This can be a very hard thing to do in practice. You probably have many experiences where what you say was misunderstood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Head of Economics and Experimentation at Zalando SE. I lead teams of social data scientists and software engineers building and evaluating large-scale automated decision-making systems, including Zalando&amp;rsquo;s A/B testing platform. I was previously a research fellow at the Institute for Quantitative Social Science, Harvard University developing statistical software for the social and physical sciences. I have held posts at City, University of London, the Hertie School of Governance, Yonsei University, and the London School of Economics where in 2012 he completed a PhD in quantitative political science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>/post/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>/post/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugo-s-built-in-shortcodes&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt; and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>/post/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de
pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>/post/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>